

KOMAL VERMA

Sector -56, Dashmesh nagar digiana, jammu, Jammu and Kashmir 180010

6006653373 | komalverma241997@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/komal-verma-84b8241ab

Profile

Associate senior executive with experience in multiple areas. Exellence in client onbording, process
improvement, formulation and development of strategies, team management. Execution and validation of
ongoing standard business process of the field. Total work experience of 20+months with startup and MNC's.

Objective

To enhance my professional skills, capabilities and knowledge in an organization which recognizes the value of hard work and trusts me with responsibilities and challenges.

Experience

Infoedge India Ltd (Jobhai.com)

03 May 2022 - Present

Associate Senior Executive

- Worked on verified, unverified, crawled jobs, agents jobs and reported jobs on CRM portal
- Handling team of 10 to 15 people and managing them.
- Submitting report of my team at the end of the day to the manager with clearing all the pendency
- Verify and detecting fraud onboarded client and blacklisting that client from the portal.
- Onboard new recruiters and making their jobs live on the portal
- o Provided functional training to the new joiners and Also assisted them to resolve their day to day queries
- Giving feedback about the portal in weekly meetings to the management
- Created a flow chart based on process of CRM for smooth functioning of portal
- Formulated new ideas and assisted in development of new strategies

Infoedge India Ltd (Jobhai.com)

Retainer

On board New clients and achieve assinged targets

- o To understand the client requirement and provide solution with good turn around
- o Publish and maintain high quality dashboard
- Handling queries and providing solutions to recruiters and jobseekers
- Handling reported jobs on CRM and taking feedbacks from recruiters and jobseekers

Internships

- Ritika Securities 12 June 2020 12 Aug 2020 HR Intern
 - Assigning Task and review performances.
 - Updating records and documentation
 - Candidate sourcing (campus) Recruitment
 - handling document and reports
 - · Scheduling meetings

21 Sept 2021 - 02 May 2022

Learnovate - 01 May 2020 - 30 May 2020 HR Intern

- · Recruiting candidate
- Scheduling and conducting interviews
- Assigning task and review performance
- · Prepare word and excel document
 - Thrice awarded with best team leader of the week

• Felis Leo venture Pvt Ltd - 15 April 2020- 15 June 2020

- HR Intern
 - · Candidate recruitment.
 - Screening resume
- · Updating records and scheduling meetings

Maruti Suzuki - 10 May 2017 - 10 July 2017 HR Intern

- Screening resume and application form
- · Updating details of new employees
- · Record handling of employees

Education

•	Dr. D. Y. Patil Vidyapeeth, Global Business School and Research Center, Tathawade pune Masters of Business Administration 7.30%	2019 - 2021
•	Dogra Degree College, Jammu(J&K) Bachelor's Degree 71%	2015 - 2018
•	Kendriya vidyalaya INS Hamla, Mumbai SSC 68%	2014 - 2015
•	Kendriya vidyalaya INS Hamla, Mumbai HSC 66%	2012 - 2013

Skills

• Critical analysis, Interpersonal skill, Effective Communication skills, TAT and Time management, Team leading and management, Employee training, Microsoft Office.

Certificates

- Digital marketing
- · Advance excel
- Design thinking
- · Best team leader
- · Entrepreneurship development program

Interests

- · Craft Work and Designing
- Communicating
- Dancing
- Photography and Video Making
- Farming

• Cooking

Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Dogri
- Punjabi

Declaration

• I hereby declare that the above -mentioned information is correct and true to the best of my knowledge.

KOMAL VERMA